<?xml version="1.0"?>
<people>
    <person id="robbo">
        <name>Robbo</name>
        <image>robbo.jpg</image>
        <service>2001-2011</service>
        <quotes>
            <quote>
                robbo: i woke up the other day covered in marmite
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                10:08 robbo: last night's checklist: get wasted, fight with paul, crash wedding, be obnoxious to a poor hardworking security guard, ride bike into lamppost, lose sunglasses<br />
                10:08 robbo: ticked em all
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote>
                rich: i'm taking a bag of mince to dempseys later in an attempt to woo that barmaid
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich: A bit gay is cool; girls love that.
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich R: "That smells like quality sausage!"
            </quote>
            <quote>
                [2:50:23 AM] Rich: i can't stop looking at the # on the top of james' penis
            </quote>
            <quote>
                [10:20:50] Rich (Prince of all developers): when is everyone going to realise that web apps are totally pointless?
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich: ok. oh yeah, i'm in the top 5% of swearers. apologies if i offended anyone...
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich: dylan! when you're fucking offline, appear offline / don't fucking appear online all the fucking time / what's fucking wrong with you? / oops / that's what happens when you sink a load of wine and try to insult prost
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich Robinson (Prince of All Developers): "I never use the thumb on anything but the bottom"
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich_r: "I like to break into mens' houses and bathe them at gunpoint."
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich_r (Prince of All Developers): "You should have heard me screaming on my kitchen floor the other week"
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich: "It's not a bag for life once you've done THAT to it..."
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                (During a conversation regarding coding styles, specifically Dan B's prefixing of params with 'p_')<br />
                Rich R: "We know about your pee, Dan B!"
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                Paul: "What the hell is that? A giant grape?"<br />
                Rich: "No... it's a plum P-L-U-M"
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote>
                Rich: "I can't take more than two balls at any one time..."
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                After picking up a pound coin in the street.<br />
                Rich R: What's the minimum amount of money you'd bend over for?
                ]]>
            </quote>
        </quotes>
    </person>
    <person id="paul">
        <name>Paul</name>
        <image>pipi.jpg</image>
        <service>2006-2011</service>
        <quotes>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                22:25 < sean> no one's logged into ORR at the moment are they?<br />
                22:26 < paul> the pirates social network?
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote1>
                <![CDATA[
                [05/03/2010 14:20:53] Paul: hi jen<br />
                [05/03/2010 14:20:59] Paul: i bring bad news<br />
                [05/03/2010 14:21:06] Paul: the toilet is rammed
                ]]>
            </quote1>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                [11:47:24] Gavin Davies: is there much difference between:<br />
                Serial ATA-300<br />
                Serial ATA-150 ?<br />
                [11:51:46] Paul: about 150
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                Paul P: This isn't rocket-science, Dylan; this is murder.
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                Carey: You need to power cycle that printer<br />
                Dave: Power cycle?!<br />
                Paul: This isn't Star Trek, Carey
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                Paul: "Man up and take a monkey to the balls!"
                ]]>
            </quote>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                <paul> in IT in school we made skynet<br />
                <paul> but when it came self aware it started touching up girls and got expelled
                ]]>
            </quote>
        </quotes>
    </person>
    <person id="john">
        <name>John</name>
        <image>john.jpg</image>
        <service>2010-2011</service>
        <quotes>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                [09:38] joncram: hi bendavies<br />
                [09:39] -->|	ben_ (~bendavies@77.108.153.99) has joined #dev<br />
                [09:39] john: psychic joncram.
                ]]>
            </quote>
        </quotes>
    </person>
    <person id="jonesy">
        <name>Jonesy</name>
        <image>jonesy.jpg</image>
        <service>2009-2011</service>
        <quotes>
            <quote>
                <![CDATA[
                14:08 (jonesy) what's the difference between CONTENT and CONETNT_45?<br />
                14:08 (rod) no idea.<br />
                14:59 Disconnected<br />
                15:41 Disconnected<br />
                16:14 (jonesy) one has _45 at the end<br />
                16:14 (rod) that was pretty much the longest joke ever<br />
                16:17 (jonesy) the longest, unfunniest joke eva!
                ]]>
            </quote>
        </quotes>
    </person>
</people>